<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Chris Turner</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Chris Turner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>0. Introduction (5 pts)  Write a narrative introductory paragraph or two describing the datasets you have chosen, the variables they contain, how they were acquired, and why they are interesting to you. Expand on potential associations you may expect, if any.  The datasets I have chosen are from the package fivethirtyeight. One of the datasets carries the statistics on the different regions and divisions in the United States and the other dataset compares hate crime to income inequality for each state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Guidelines and Rubric  0. (5 pts) Introduce your dataset and each of your variables (or just your main variables if you have lots) in a paragraph. What are they measuring? How many observations?
The dataset I have chosen contains 9 variables and 601 observations for data on extramarital affairs. These varibales include sex, age, number of years married, whether they have children, religiosity, level of education, occupation (according to Hollingshead’s classification), self rating on the happiness of their marriage, and number of estramarital “encounters” during the past year with each observation being a single individual.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
